<resources>
    <string name="app_name">StoryTeller</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_the_world_full_of_stories">Welcome To The World Full Of Stories!</string>
    <string name="this_app_is_developed_with_by_codeites">This App is Developed with ❤ By CODEITES</string>

    <string name="thirstycrow_head">The Thirsty Crow Story</string>

    <string name="thirstycrow_story">It was a hot summer’s day. A thirsty crow flew into a village in search of water. The crow flew over the houses, fields, and trees. But he didn’t find any water. After a long time, he came across a farm. Under one of the trees on the farm was a pitcher of water.
Happy that he found some water finally, he swooped down to the tree and then down to the ground. He quickly moved towards the pitcher and looked inside. There was very little water in the pot. The crow put his beak inside the pitcher but could not reach the water. The water level was too low, and the narrow opening prevented his neck from going all the way down.

He tried to push the vessel down to let the water out, but it was too heavy. The crow was disappointed. He was really thirsty and needed a drink of water badly. He could have given up and flown to another farm, looking for water.
But he didn’t. Instead, he looked around and thought, “What else can I do?” He saw that there were a lot of pebbles on the farm. And, he had an idea! He collected a pebble and put it into the pitcher. He collected another pebble and another and put them all in the pitcher. As he added more and more stones, the water level came up to the brim.</string>

    <string name="akbarbirbal_head">Akbar and Birbal</string>

    <string name="akbarbirbal_story">One day, king Akbar asked a question in his court that left everyone in the courtroom puzzled. As they all tried to figure out the answer, Birbal walked in and asked what the matter was. They repeated the question to him.

The question was, “How many crows are there in the city?”
Birbal immediately smiled and went up to Akbar. He announced the answer; he said there were twenty-one thousand, five hundred and twenty-three crows in the city. When asked how he knew the answer, Birbal replied, “Ask your men to count the number of crows. If there are more, then the relatives of the crows must be visiting them from nearby cities. If there are fewer, then the crows from our city must be visiting their relatives who live outside the city.” Pleased with the answer, Akbar presented Birbal with a ruby and pearl chain.

Moral of the Story

Having an explanation for your answer is just as important as having an answer.</string>

    <string name="rabbitturtle_head">Rabbit and Turtle</string>

    <string name="rabbitturtle_story">One day a rabbit was boasting about how fast he could run. He was laughing at the turtle for being so slow. Much to the rabbit’s surprise, the turtle challenged him to a race. The rabbit thought this was a good joke and accepted the challenge. The fox was to be the umpire of the race. As the race began, the rabbit raced way ahead of the turtle, just like everyone thought.

The rabbit got to the halfway point and could not see the turtle anywhere. He was hot and tired and decided to stop and take a short nap. Even if the turtle passed him, he would be able to race to the finish line ahead of him. All this time the turtle kept walking step by step by step. He never quit no matter how hot or tired he got. He just kept going.

However, the rabbit slept longer than he had thought and woke up. He could not see the turtle anywhere! He went at full speed to the finish line but found the turtle there waiting for him.

Moral: never underestimate the weakest opponent.</string>


    <string name="storkcrab_head">Stork and Crab</string>

    <string name="storkcrab_story">Once upon a time, there lived a stork who used to pick fishes from the pond beside him, and eat them. However, as he grew older, he found it difficult to catch a single fish. In order to feed himself, he thought of a plan. He told the fish, frogs, and crabs, that some men are planning to fill the pond and grow crops, and that’s why there won’t be any fish in the pond. He also told them how sad he felt about this and that he will miss them all. The fish were sad and asked the stork to help them. The stork promised to take all of them to a bigger pond. However, he told them, “As I am old, I can take only a few of you at one go.” The stork would take the fishes to a rock, kill them, and eat them up. Every time he was hungry, he would take a few of them to the rock and eat them.
There lived a crab in the pond, who wanted to go to the bigger pond too. The stork thought of eating the crab for a change and agreed on helping him. On the way, the crab asked the stork, “Where is the big pond?” The stork laughed and pointed to the rock, which was filled with fish bones. The crab realised that the stork would kill him, and so quickly thought of a plan to save himself. He caught the stork’s neck and did not let it go until the stork died.


Moral of the Story: Always have a presence of mind and act quickly when in danger.</string>

    <string name="friendshunter_head">Four Friends and Hunter</string>

    <string name="friendshunter_story">A deer, a turtle, a crow and a rat were friends. They lived happily in a jungle. One day, the deer was caught in a hunter’s trap and the friends made a plan to save him. The deer struggled as if it was in pain and then it lie motionless, with eyes wide open, as if it were dead. The crow and the other birds then sat on the deer and started poking it as they do to a dead animal.
Right then, the turtle crossed the hunter’s path to distract him. The hunter left the deer, assuming it dead, and went after the turtle. Meanwhile, the rat chew open the net to free the deer while the crow picked up the turtle and quickly took it away from the hunter.
Moral: Teamwork can achieve great results.</string>

    <string name="mongoosewife_head"> The Mongoose And The Brahmin’s Wife</string>

    <string name="mongoosewife_story">A brahmin, his wife, and his baby boy lived in a small village. They had a pet mongoose which lived with them. One day, when the brahmin was out on chores, his wife left the baby in the cradle and went to fetch a pot of water. She asked the mongoose to take care of the baby while she is away. As the mongoose guarded the baby, it saw a snake crawling into the house. It soon attacked the snake and killed it.
As soon as the brahmin’s wife entered with the pot of water, the mongoose happily welcomed her with blood all over her mouth. The lady was terrified at the sight and assumed that the mongoose had killed the baby. Furious, the lady dropped the pot of water on the mongoose and beat it to death with a stick. Then she went inside and found the baby happily playing in the cradle.
The lady realized what she had done and repented for acting without thought.
Moral: Do not act in haste without understanding the situation.</string>

    <string name="jackaldrum_head">The Jackal And The Drum</string>

    <string name="jackaldrum_story">One day, a hungry jackal wandered into a deserted battlefield in search of food. The place had nothing but a drum that the army left behind. When the wind blew, the branches of a tree moved and hit the drum, making a loud noise. The jackal was scared and decided to run from there. On second thoughts, he decided to explore the noise. As he drew closer to the sound, he found the drum and realized that it was harmless. When he approached the drum, he found food nearby.
Moral: Do not react blindly with fear.</string>


    <string name="goatsjackal_head">Goats And Jackal</string>
    <string name="goatsjackal_story">A jackal was once passing by a village, when it saw two strong goats fighting with each other. The goats were surrounded by people who were cheering for them. A few minutes into the fight, the goats had bruises on the body and were bleeding a little. This jackal was drawn to the smell of blood and wanted to get a bite of the goats’ flesh. It jumped at the goats at once, without thinking.
The two goats were stronger than the jackal and mercilessly trampled on the animal and killed it.
Moral: Think before you jump.</string>

    <string name="lionmouse_head">The Lion and The Mouse</string>

    <string name="lionmouse_story">A lion was sleeping in a forest. A mouse started playing on it. The lion was disturbed and arose from his sleep. It caught up the mouse angrily and tried to crush it to death. Then the mouse prayed the lion to leave him off and assured that it would help him when it needed. The lion laughed at it and let him off.One day the lion was caught in a net spread by a hunter. It roared and tried to escape but in vain. The mouse heared the lions roaring and came there. It started cutting the net with its teeth. The lion escaped and thanked the mouse. MORAL : Everything has its own value.</string>

    <string name="tortoisegeese_head">The Tortoise and the Geese</string>
    <string name="tortoisegeese_story">Once upon a time, beside a lake, there lived a tortoise and two geese who were great friends. As the lake was drying, the geese decided to migrate to a new place. The tortoise also wanted to move with them, but he couldn’t fly, and so he pleaded the geese to take him with them. After trying really hard to convince them, finally, the geese agreed. They held a stick with their beaks and asked the tortoise to hold the stick with his mouth, warning him to not open his mouth and let go of the stick.

As they flew high, some onlookers thought that the tortoise was kidnapped and commented: “Oh, the poor tortoise!” This angered the tortoise and he immediately opened his mouth to say something back. As soon as he did, he fell to the ground and died.
Moral of the Story: Think before you speak. Listen to instructions, and follow them.</string>

    <string name="threefish_head">A Tale of Three Fish</string>
    <string name="threefish_story">In a lake, there were three fish who were great friends. The first fish was very smart, the second one knew how to find his way out of trouble, and the third was adamant and hated changes. The first fish overheard a fisherman’s conversation about coming back the next day and fishing in the lake. Sensing danger, he cautioned his friends to move out of the lake. The second fish said, “I will stay here and find a way out if I’m caught.” The third fish said, “I do not want to move out. I will remain here, and if I have to get caught, I will.” The first fish moved out. The next day, the fisherman arrived and caught the other two fish. The second one cleverly escaped by pretending to be dead. The third fish did nothing and got caught and died.
Moral of the Story: One should always be open to change and adapt accordingly. Take immediate action when you sense danger.</string>

    <string name="lionrabbit_head">The Foolish Lion and the Clever Rabbit</string>
    <string name="lionrabbit_story">Once upon a time, there lived a greedy lion who attacked and killed animals, because of which every animal in the jungle was very afraid of him. One day, they decided that each animal would go to the lion, per day, as his prey. The lion agreed. When it was the rabbit’s turn, they decided to send the wise old one. He travelled slowly and reached the lion’s den before sunset. The lion furiously asked him, “Why are you so late?” The rabbit answered, ”A group of rabbits were coming to you, but on their way, the others were attacked by another ferocious lion. I managed to escape and came here.” The rabbit also mentioned that the other lion was challenging this one.
The lion was extremely angry and asked the rabbit to take him to meet the new lion. The wise rabbit took the lion to a deep well, and showed him his own reflection. As the lion growled, his reflection did the same. He considered this reflection to be his enemy. The enraged lion jumped into the well to attack the other lion, and ended up dying. Thus, the wise old rabbit saved himself, and all the animals in the forest.



Moral of the Story: One must always focus on solutions, rather than problems.</string>

    <string name="elephantsparrow_head">The Elephant and the Sparrows</string>
    <string name="elephantsparrow_story">A sparrow couple had a beautiful nest with eggs, on a tall, strong tree, and were expecting their little ones soon. However, an arrogant elephant soon visited the area and shook the tree so hard, that he managed to destroy the nest and the eggs. Angered and saddened by this, the sparrows decided to seek revenge.


They asked their woodpecker friend to help them. The woodpecker, along with his friends, the fly and the frog, devised a plan. The frog asked the fly to buzz near the elephant’s ear. He said, “When the elephant closes his eyes, woodpecker, you must pierce his eyes. The elephant will stand up and try to find water. I will croak far away and the elephant will think there’s water around and reach the place. We will create a big pit and the elephant will fall into it.”
At sunset, they worked as per the plan, and the elephant fell into the pit and died.
Moral of the Story: It’s not physical strength and haughtiness that wins, but intelligence and teamwork that matters.</string>

    <string name="bundlestick_head">A Bundle of Sticks</string>
    <string name="bundlestick_story">Once upon a time, three neighbours living in a village were having trouble with their crops. Each of the neighbours had one field, but the crops on their fields were infested with pests and were wilting. Every day, they would come up with different ideas to help their crops. The first one tried using a scarecrow in his field, the second used pesticides, and the third built a fence on his field, all to no avail.
One day, the village head came by and called the three farmers. He gave them each a stick and asked them to break it. The farmers could break them easily. He then gave them a bundle of three sticks, and again, asked them to break it. This time, the farmers struggled to break the sticks. The village head said, “Together, you are stronger and work better than you do it alone.” The farmers understood what the village head was saying. They pooled in their resources and got rid of the pests from their fields.

Moral of the Story

There is strength in unity.</string>

    <string name="bearfriends_head">The Bear and Two Friends</string>
    <string name="bearfriends_story">One day, two best friends were walking on a lonely and dangerous path through a jungle. As the sun began to set, they grew afraid but held on to each other. Suddenly, they saw a bear in their path. One of the boys ran to the nearest tree and climbed it in a jiffy. The other boy did not know how to climb the tree by himself, so he lay on the ground, pretending to be dead. The bear approached the boy on the ground and sniffed around his head. After appearing to whisper something in the boy’s ear, the bear went on its way. The boy on the tree climbed down and asked his friend what the bear had whispered in his ear. He replied, “Do not trust friends who do not care for you.”

Moral of the Story

A friend in need is a friend indeed.</string>



</resources>
